[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "I don't think you two have ever been together for a primetime interview, have you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "two", "have", "ever", "been", "together", "for", "a", "primetime", "interview", ",", "have", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "No, actually, we haven't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "actually", ",", "we", "have", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "How long have you been together?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "have", "you", "been", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Eight years.", "answer_tokens": ["Eight", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Do you know -- do you feel like you're having the last laugh for all those who mocked it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "--", "do", "you", "feel", "like", "you", "'re", "having", "the", "last", "laugh", "for", "all", "those", "who", "mocked", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, I feel like anyone who is sort of engaging themselves in tabloid press as fact will -- you know you'll always have the last laugh.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "feel", "like", "anyone", "who", "is", "sort", "of", "engaging", "themselves", "in", "tabloid", "press", "as", "fact", "will", "--", "you", "know", "you", "'ll", "always", "have", "the", "last", "laugh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "How do you make it work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "make", "it", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, one, I think you have to make your relationship a priority.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", ",", "I", "think", "you", "have", "to", "make", "your", "relationship", "a", "priority", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Is he -- is he romantic?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "--", "is", "he", "romantic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "I would say so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Or is he ruggedly you know?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "he", "ruggedly", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "No, he's very --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "'s", "very", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Tucked you over his shoulder and wheel you home for dinner?", "question_tokens": ["Tucked", "you", "over", "his", "shoulder", "and", "wheel", "you", "home", "for", "dinner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "I think he's a little bit -- I think he's a little bit of both.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "a", "little", "bit", "--", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "What's your favorite Post-It note?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "favorite", "Post-It", "note", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Wow, my favorite.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", ",", "my", "favorite", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "You are a little old softie, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "a", "little", "old", "softie", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Are you happy with how he's gone on?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "happy", "with", "how", "he", "'s", "gone", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "When you first got into this, did you ever imagine it would become a primary new source in that way?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "first", "got", "into", "this", ",", "did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "it", "would", "become", "a", "primary", "new", "source", "in", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "What are the rules?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "rules", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "The rules -- the phone goes down at dinner.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "rules", "--", "the", "phone", "goes", "down", "at", "dinner", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "But isn't it slightly perverse?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "n't", "it", "slightly", "perverse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "It is slightly perverse.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "slightly", "perverse", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "How big of a factor was it that you've got three young girls yourself and you could look at them and perhaps see them transplanted into this hideous world?", "question_tokens": ["How", "big", "of", "a", "factor", "was", "it", "that", "you", "'ve", "got", "three", "young", "girls", "yourself", "and", "you", "could", "look", "at", "them", "and", "perhaps", "see", "them", "transplanted", "into", "this", "hideous", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, the average age of entry into the sex trade is 13 years old, and that's globally.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "average", "age", "of", "entry", "into", "the", "sex", "trade", "is", "13", "years", "old", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "globally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Why was that, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "was", "that", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Well, I think that there's -- I think that there's a subsect of what we're looking at it and it's sort of dangerously bleeds over into something that people are very accustomed to.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "there", "'s", "--", "I", "think", "that", "there", "'s", "a", "subsect", "of", "what", "we", "'re", "looking", "at", "it", "and", "it", "'s", "sort", "of", "dangerously", "bleeds", "over", "into", "something", "that", "people", "are", "very", "accustomed", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Prostitution?", "question_tokens": ["Prostitution", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "What do you think about that conundrum?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "about", "that", "conundrum", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "That's why we're using social media for this campaign, is to actually go right into the heart of where it's taking place.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "why", "we", "'re", "using", "social", "media", "for", "this", "campaign", ",", "is", "to", "actually", "go", "right", "into", "the", "heart", "of", "where", "it", "'s", "taking", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "And so was he deceitful in the kind of person that he described himself as?", "question_tokens": ["And", "so", "was", "he", "deceitful", "in", "the", "kind", "of", "person", "that", "he", "described", "himself", "as", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "He lied to me about his age.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "lied", "to", "me", "about", "his", "age", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "I mean is this a familiar story of how these things start?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "is", "this", "a", "familiar", "story", "of", "how", "these", "things", "start", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "No, what she's describing is -- I mean the stories do start to take on a very similar kind of framework with the pimp.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "what", "she", "'s", "describing", "is", "--", "I", "mean", "the", "stories", "do", "start", "to", "take", "on", "a", "very", "similar", "kind", "of", "framework", "with", "the", "pimp", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "And what did he put you through?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "he", "put", "you", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Well, at first he told me, you know, I'll take you shopping and I will give you anything that you want and I'll take you out of the life that you're in.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "at", "first", "he", "told", "me", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'ll", "take", "you", "shopping", "and", "I", "will", "give", "you", "anything", "that", "you", "want", "and", "I", "'ll", "take", "you", "out", "of", "the", "life", "that", "you", "'re", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "What was going on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "At first it was just him, and then when I had escaped to get home, I had to call somebody.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "first", "it", "was", "just", "him", ",", "and", "then", "when", "I", "had", "escaped", "to", "get", "home", ",", "I", "had", "to", "call", "somebody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "And how old were you then?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "old", "were", "you", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "I was around 14, 15.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "around", "14", ",", "15", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "EX", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Finally, what would you say to other girls who find themselves in the same kind of situation?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "to", "other", "girls", "who", "find", "themselves", "in", "the", "same", "kind", "of", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I would tell them to go to an adult that is trustworthy, and that would listen to them, and that they're worthwhile waiting on, and they have a lot of people that do care about them, and that is there for them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "tell", "them", "to", "go", "to", "an", "adult", "that", "is", "trustworthy", ",", "and", "that", "would", "listen", "to", "them", ",", "and", "that", "they", "'re", "worthwhile", "waiting", "on", ",", "and", "they", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "that", "do", "care", "about", "them", ",", "and", "that", "is", "there", "for", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "You know, this a multi-faceted form of abuse, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "this", "a", "multi-faceted", "form", "of", "abuse", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "And then the abuse continues.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "then", "the", "abuse", "continues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "How do those girls without the help of organizations like yourselves ever get out of that cycle?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "those", "girls", "without", "the", "help", "of", "organizations", "like", "yourselves", "ever", "get", "out", "of", "that", "cycle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "How much money is the U.S. government spending on, say, policing drugs compared to sex slavery?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "money", "is", "the", "U.S.", "government", "spending", "on", ",", "say", ",", "policing", "drugs", "compared", "to", "sex", "slavery", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Great question, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", "question", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "If you were in charge of policy in this area, what is the key thing that should be done?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "in", "charge", "of", "policy", "in", "this", "area", ",", "what", "is", "the", "key", "thing", "that", "should", "be", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Well, first, look, the reason why we've initiated this campaign is we have to create awareness.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", ",", "look", ",", "the", "reason", "why", "we", "'ve", "initiated", "this", "campaign", "is", "we", "have", "to", "create", "awareness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ"], "qSentId": 529, "question": "I mean, could you be in this for 30 years?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "could", "you", "be", "in", "this", "for", "30", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Probably longer,", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "longer,"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 553, "question": "What are you up to now movie-wise?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "up", "to", "now", "movie-wise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "I just finished a movie called \"New Year's Eve.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "finished", "a", "movie", "called", "``", "New", "Year", "'s", "Eve", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Has that taken over in priorities for both of you?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "that", "taken", "over", "in", "priorities", "for", "both", "of", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Yes, I --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]